On
Shatch Carnival was held at LINE Cube Shibuya on February 25.
Thanks for your hard work.
Thank you to everyone who came.
Today is the, the completion game.
Let's talk, let's talk.
After the event, we'll have the finish line first, right?
Yes, in the dressing room.
In the dressing room.
Let's talk about what we talked about then, and let's talk about it again.
But for now, I'm just saying it was good.
It was good for now.
It was fun.
It was super fun.
Thank you very much.
I'm happy to hear that.
Because, you know, LINE Forward is always aiming for 100 points.
But there are times when you have an "aha" moment. You know...
I mean, it's just not right for us.
But this time, LINE CUBE seemed to be very genuine.
Did you have fun? Was it fun?
It was fun!
It was fun! came out first.
There were the members.
It was fun.
The live show itself was a bit like a story.
Hou-chan was also responding to the story of LINE Catch at first.
The venue was not Shibuya, but Gokusha-machiya.
Gokushamachiya was an incitement, wasn't it?
Did he?
Did he encourage the audience?
No, something else, Gokumachiya.
You want to talk about it?
We had only found out about the show the day before.
Wasn't it?
Yes, that's right.
I received a message before the show saying, "That's the story, isn't it? I had received a message before the concert saying, "That's the story, isn't it?
I didn't see the whole video until the day before the show, so it was last minute.
Goshamachiya.
We talked about how we shouldn't stir things up after getting to know each other because it was Gokusha Machiya, and we made sure we were all on the same page.
He said don't protect the world view.
They said we have to protect our worldview.
Today, from the extreme Burning Festival, Gosha Machiya!
Yay!
Wasn't that infinitely fast?
No, seriously. Everyone was so flexible.
You were the pine tree people of Gokurumachoya, weren't you?
Yes, yes, he was a resident.
It was nice.
Yes, it was amazing.
And it's always this carnival that's held once a year.
It was a story that everyone should take a camera and play the carnival! It was a story about a carnival that always takes place once a year, and everyone was encouraged to play it on camera.
Everyone really took off their masks.
We were able to take off the masks.
We took off our masks from the very beginning.
Too fast to take off the masks.
Were you able to take them off?
I couldn't.
I knew it.
You couldn't take it off, right?
It didn't come off.
Did you notice?
I don't know. I couldn't even see the person next to me.
Well, I was the first one to take it off, then Kosan, then Yuzuki, then Shunsui, in order of parts.
I was the first one to take it off, then Kosan, then Yuzuki, then Shunsui, in that order.
And then the strings were untied.
That's why I felt it the tightest.
I thought I could untie it and take it off, but I couldn't.
It was like a necklace on top.
Oh, really?
Yes, I couldn't get it off.
It came off from my face.
So I wondered how everyone else was doing.
I did that too.
Was it the same?
During the rehearsal, we did the whole process from the opening when everyone put on the masks until the masks were taken off.
It was done.
Yes, it was done, and only the second time Chunsui failed, I told everyone.
I told everyone that I had done the mask.
I told them I was going to do it from the front.
Then it was the same as before.
It became crumpled and hard.
I didn't do it, but on the contrary, it got kind of hard.
And I couldn't get it off, so I thought, "What am I going to do?
I didn't even realize it was happening.
But it was on?
You two didn't show it on your faces.
Oh, thank God.
I didn't see it on your face.
I was so nervous.
I think everyone just found out about it.
Thank God.
I could see their faces.
I was able to show their faces.
I couldn't show them my face.
Oh, no... oh, no... oh, no...
Accident, accident, accident.
It was an accident.
It's been here the whole time.
People.
One person.One is.
A normal, cold person.
That sucks.
But if I don't get this one.
I was thinking of taking it off at the A-melody.
As an image.
For sure.
How you figured it out, that's great.
You figured it out.
The power of 10 years.
It's kind of the first song.
Oh no, oh no.
The first song and, you know, the blue ariat of the motionanancier.
The first song was only the third song.
That's only the first number of times.
But the last one had an impact.
You haven't been analyzed?
Analyzed.
And then after that, it was shatch chance corner, right?
Yes, I saw it.
Everyone saw it.
I saw it. Thank you.
You know, the videos and the pictures.
You took pictures from various angles.
All kinds of angles.
So, I can see it like this from here.
That's right.
There are pictures of stones and close-ups.
Thank you.
We had fun. We had fun.
It was fun.
And the dancers were super cool.
From one crop.
It was amazing.
Self-talk?
It was my own language.
There was Twilight's answer.
What's that?
The good life?
Walpurgis, that's what you get after "the good life.
Yeah, that's right.
Walpurgis is a four-person show.
First time.
Good.
Have there been a lot of cartoons?
There are a lot of them.
The song itself is called Walpurgis.
The time is good.
It fits.
The world view was perfect.
It was perfect for that concert.
The beautiful girls were perfect for the song.
It was fun.
It's a fun song.
I wonder how they grow up?
I don't know!
But you know, many people like it. Balbrinth.
The last chorus, toe-toot-toot, and then oi! Oi! Oi! Oi! I want the person who made the song to do it.
I saw the person who made the song do it.
I saw him doing it.
For real? What?
Everyone has a good ear.
They're rather straight.
Right?
No one sounds like they can hear.
The guy gets the last rustle, and then he goes, "Oi! Oi! And that's it?
And is that it? It's very difficult.
Maybe it's too hard.
Wait, it's amazing.
It's not so much that it hurts. It's just that one of them was like...
I thought, "Wow, that's great.
Wow, that guy's amazing.
Let's find him.
As for the original tax, it's only a thin stroke.
Let's push it.
I want you to do it.
It's a little difficult because it's in the back.
I've been asked to keep the water.
When you have stroked it, please try it, everyone.
Please do it.
It's cute, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
It's cute.
And I haven't seen the highlights in a while. It was cute. It was cute. The moon in the background adds to the world. Yes, it did.
It matched the images. Everything was in sync.
It's nice to have a monitor, isn't it? Yes, it really is.
It was great that I could see what I saw. I could see the members too.
I was looking at them a lot when I turned around. Yeah, I was looking at them a lot.
I was looking at them when they were turning around. I was looking at them so much.
I thought to myself, "I'm looking at them so much.
I'm looking at it. I would look at it.
That's how I feel. It's like "Aru Aru. It's "Aru Aru".
So, what's next?
The boss? No. Race.
Lace light. Yes, lace.
You were rocking it. It's amazing, isn't it?
It's like Walpoleek.
Highlight. Highlight.Highlights. Highlight.
This show of lace light. The power of expression.
Joerges was great. Yes, it was.
It was Joerg, wasn't it? That's right.
You showed two songs at a time. It was something like that.
There were a lot of developments.
It was amazing.
The lace curtains were shaking.
It was shaking.
It was shaking so much.
There was a staff member who had been with us for a long time and had graduated.
There was a staff member who had been with us for many years who had graduated.
Recently, I was reminded of that.
I really remembered it and it was bad.
It was worse at the end of the day.
Yay!
I tried my best not to remember that part.
Nice lyrics.
Yes, it's a good song. That's why I was feeling a little more emotionally involved in the song.
But every time I play "Hikari," I think about it.
I'm glad you wrote such a great song.
Everyone is doing this.
I'm so happy to hear it in everyone's voice.
Everyone is singing this.
It's so different. The members sing the songs they wrote.
Our feelings are totally different.
We can relate to it.
Every time we play it, I think it's a good song.
It's a good song.
When we wrote it then, it was a two-time experience of this kind of feeling.
It's different just at that time.
Even though a lot of time has passed, it matches what I'm thinking now.
Even when the other person says it, it matches.
We match together.
Amazing!
He's the god of empathy serving.
It's as if he's been watching over everything.
That's amazing.
Our own staff is here.
I didn't think so, but now.
Even from the staff.
They said the light was terrible.
Just during the criticism.
Yes, that's right.
Was that part of the intense blocking?
It was a nice flow.
It was nice, that part.
The director from that point on, it was amazing.
It would have been very difficult if he had been emotional.
It was really hard.
It was a tough time with the director.
I was really happy with Hikari.
Then, I forgot about it, and the director came to me.
He was getting drunk or something.
And then, something like...
"One, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one...
You know that sound in front of the director?
That sound is played.
I thought, "Oh, it's all the bosses.
I was just in time to get out of there.
It was really the time of the day.
The time of the day.
I was kind of getting lip glossed.
Yes, I was getting drunk.
I had totally forgotten about it.
It was like this, this kind of thing.
The makeup artist doesn't know when I'm going to leave.
So let's put on lipstick.
Yuko, you wait 10 minutes.
Whenever you have it.
Same thing.
Do the same thing.
I never got to see the whole rehearsal there.
Hikari is done.
You can wear them from the middle.
We wear them from the middle, and then we go up the sleeve stairs and meet on the second floor.
In between, there was a time of...
I knew it would be too much if there were four floors.
Yes, that's right.
When I say "four floors".
I'm like, "Wow!".
Even downstairs.
I thought, "Ah.
And then, "Ha!
Isn't that bad?
There's not much of a problem.
I came out of the stairwell.
I thought I noticed it.
Upstairs.
I thought it would be bad if I just went this way.
I was coming out from the front, and we were coming out at the same time.
That was good.
We saw each other.
We did the same thing.
It's different when you go to a live concert.
And then there are the members.
It's different because they're there.
They were dancing so tough.
It was really nice.
Thank you so much.
Your dad was so cool.Dad was cool.
He was really cool.
I'll see you again.
That was the coolest thing I've ever seen.
You were the Rocky of all time.
It was so rockin'.
It's fun to feel like you've been pounded by the other members of the group.
Butoh parades are fun, but it's a burning, melting sensation, so it's not so much fun, it's more like...hmmm...
But Momochan's patreo was so amazing that I laughed.
I was laughing because Momochan's patreo was so amazing.
GUNJUBARAN. I laughed so hard.
There is no switch like that.
There are many switches.
Sometimes I can understand them, but not this way.
You can't tell if I like it this way or that way?
Wait, the bowling line.
Oh, we haven't done that yet? Not yet.
He wants you to do it.
He wants one of us to stir it up at the "I'm not a fan of this" part.
Let's do it again.
I asked Momochan to do it, and she did.
I thought she was going to be like, "Wan, wan, I'm going to do something.
Forne, forne, forne, forne, forne, forne, forne, forne, forne, forne, forne, forne, forne, forne, forne, forne, forne, forne, forne, forne, forne.
And then something amazing happens, like, "If I do this, I'm going to get it.
And you just have to go to the front.
So, why don't you just go ahead and...
Forne, forne, forne.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You know, I thought he was going to go for it.
I'm okay now.
I'm really impressed.
We're going to be super-dollars.
It's really hard!
It was great!
You know, these parts...
You know those songs that make you want to go to Fornay?
I got used to it again, so I did it again.
I got used to it again.
I thought, "I've got to keep up with the others
I thought, "I have to do it well to keep up with everyone.
But I also wanted to do this.
I want to do this!
I want to go forward, but I don't want to change.
I want to do the morning look.
You know, I think I'm the one smiling from the take.
It's too much, and the emotion is kind of...
It's getting easier.
It was so good.
It was really good.
But Ho-chan has done it twice before, right?
You've done it twice before, right?
Starlast Morning Hall.
Wait!
Is that a good thing?
It's a very good thing.
That's what I usually do.
That's what usually happens.
It's just suddenly happening.
That's great.
That's really good.
The switch is easy to understand.
It's really easy to understand.
Everyone is talking about it.
It's too easy to understand.
Everyone understands it.
I'm telling you now.
The one time we've had one of these in the past.
Starlust Morning.
What was it?
Oh, that one.
What was the show?
What was it?
The camera vest.
I remember from before.
It's only happened a few times in the past.
In 10 years.
That's amazing.
You've got it.
Ten years.
One of those times came, right?
It was one time.
That's amazing.
Once in 5 years.
Once every five years.
It's not good at all.
They don't come at all.
Even then.
I remember being pulled in so much that I could do it at the highest tension.
I remember laughing as well as being amazed.
But it was great.
It was good, very good.
Genius.
When I was naming it.
That moniker mode.
Monoca pro, right?
I want to see it every time.
It's just rarer than shoulders.
That's why the girls get more excited than we do.
That level, that moment in time.
It's amazing.That's great.
The analogy between Buchopa and us was so good it made me shiver.
And then...
We were on the second floor, right?
We were doing the buchopa and then we went downstairs.
We'd turn around and do the buchopas.
Everyone was looking at Honoka's face.
Us.
I can't stand it.
It was really cool.
It's true.
It's true. He was really cool.
He was like Oyasama.
It was the best.
He was so cool.
I'm looking forward to the next Buchoppa.
But, someone who isn't cool is in Buchoppa.
That's just too bad.
They are there every time.
The bar is being raised higher and higher.
They are too good.
So, everyone's bochoppa brought out the best in me.
Everyone's Buchoppa?
You know when to do something.
That's right.
That's true.
They were excited.
They're going "wow".
Wow, the clincher.
Maybe...
If Lahmin is okay with this.
I might be able to see it.
It's gonna get worse, isn't it?
You mean we'll see more?
Yes, yes, yes.
That's right.
But they won't know yet.
It's great to be scared.
It really is.
It's true.
The match you waved in my hand was amazing.
That was great.
It was cool.
Buchoppa was great.
Following the song, "Dreama" was great.
Dreama was good.
Yes, American, followed by Dreama was good.
It's pretty good.
Rachmin.
Now that's what I'm talking about. The lyrics are great, too.
Yeah, it was a good song.
The last part of the song, "Shine brighter and brighter.
I put too much effort into it.
I couldn't dance.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Because!
What's that?
I never said that before.
You danced?
I didn't.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I might have!
Hey, hey, hey.
Dream is, you know, a little soft.
I'm going back.
You saw what we just did.
This?
Yeah.
Oh, my God!
Laugh it up!
That moment when we put our shoulders together.
I do it all the time.
It's like, you're already into it.
You know what I mean?
Bang!
It's definitely different.
Very sharp.
You could say that.
I can do smart.
Yeah. Yeah.
That's why I didn't go with you.
We didn't...
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
It was business as usual.
Yeah.
It was fine.
It was so much fun.
That was great.
Yeah, it was.
We were doing it.
I couldn't dance.
I couldn't speak.
I lost my crouch, and now I'm stuck in it, too.
We lost our crouch.
More and more.Much, much more.
He's a singer. It's not crazy.
It was safe.
It's just that someone who's a lot slower... suddenly did this.
I knew you'd get it. I knew you'd get it.
That was amazing.
My first time at White's.
That was fun.
White and I... we had a happy live encore.
And the parade was great.
That was the last time I heard your voice.
I'm sure it was today.
I'm sure it was.
I can't wait to hear it.
I wrote that song just to get my voice out.
That's right.
It's hard to do today that I want to do.
I have to do it to do it.
I have to do it.
Well then, I guess the announcement is done.
We're holding a shirt summer at Nagoya Castle on July 22nd!
Wow!
I'm so happy!
The place where it all began.
It's going to be hot with matches there.
Because we don't have any more shirts up there.
Nothing! Nothing!
Nagoya Castle in summer
It's hard work.
But I wonder if it can be waterproofed?
I don't know if they can.
But in a year like this...
It was announced that the ban would be lifted this year.
It's been announced that the ban will be lifted this year.
I think we'll be able to hear it at Shirt Summer.
I'm sure you'll be able to hear it at Shirt Summer.
You have a lot of songs with your voice.
Yes, we do.
So most of the songs after we changed our name to Shirts
I haven't been able to perform most of them
I haven't been able to perform them out loud
So we've been talking a lot about what we're going to do about that.
We've been talking about it a lot.
I've never seen a shirt with a voice.
That's right.
And you liked it.
And these songs are going to grow from there, especially the ones we've already performed.
But they're going to be even more fun. Oh my God.
What's going to happen? I don't think we'll see this camesso often.
I think it's gonna be fun. More?
No, it'll be easier to turn it on if we can call it.
I'm looking forward to it. I'm so looking forward to it.
Show us your fantasies, too. Of course.
Of course, of course, of course. Suddenly it's for me.
Of course, of course, of course, of course, of course, of course, of course. Suddenly you're so confident.
I'm looking forward to it.
July 22nd. I'm sure we'll have more details on tickets and stuff, so just keep your schedules straight.
I'm looking forward to it. I'm looking forward to it.
But it's a one-man show, and the next one-man show is on that shirt.
So, yeah, it's not too far away, but we have a lot of events until then.
We've got a lot of events until then, and we've got to test our voice.
Let's have fun!
Thank you very much for the LINE cube!
Thank you very much. Thank you for all the comments.
I'd love to hear your comments on the shirt!
Please send us lots of comments and good buttons!
And please subscribe to our channel!
That's all for now.
Bye bye. Thank you.
[ED]